whenu.com 2007-12-24

# WhenU.com - Consumers

WhenU.com, Inc. ("WhenU") respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this privacy policy carefully so that you understand the ways in which we use and protect the information that we collect through our Web site located at www.whenu.com (the "Web Site").

This privacy policy applies only to the information that we collect through our Web Site. To review the privacy policies that apply to other Web sites operated by WhenU, including www.pricebandit.com, www.getweathercast.com, and www.whenushop.com, please visit those Web sites and click on the applicable privacy link. Separate privacy policies apply to the various software products that can be purchased or downloaded through this Web Site. For the privacy policies that apply to our software products, including SAVE, WeatherCast, SearchBar, and others, please access www.whenu.com/privacy.html and review the privacy policy and end user license agreement (EULA) for the applicable product.

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this privacy policy or the privacy practices applicable to WhenU's operation of this Web Site, please contact us at:

**Email:[privacy@whenumail.com](mailto:privacy@whenumail.com)  
Telephone: 866-WHENU-11**

You may also write to:

**Attention: Privacy Policy  
WhenU.com, Inc.  
1 Penn Plaza, Suite 4532  
New York, NY 10119  
U.S.A.**

The following Quick Links are provided to help you more easily navigate this page.

Quick Links: 

  * What is WhenU's philosophy regarding online privacy?
  * How does WhenU protect children's privacy?
  * What types of information does the WhenU Web Site collect and how is it used?
  * How is information shared with third parties?
  * How does WhenU safeguard my personally-identifiable information?
  * How can I review, change or delete my information?
  * How will WhenU notify users of changes to this privacy policy?

**WHENU'S PHILOSOPHY REGARDING ONLINE PRIVACY**

Consumer privacy is of the utmost importance to our business. Therefore, WhenU adheres to the following strict guidelines to protect your privacy:

  * WhenU will NOT collect any personally-identifiable information about you except for information that you voluntarily provide. 
  * WhenU will NOT create any browsing profile for you or your individual machine. 
  * WhenU will NOT engage in any sort of user profiling. 
  * WhenU will NOT download and install software on you machine without your consent. 

Back to top

**PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CHILDREN**

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses and phone numbers) over the Internet, to WhenU or to anyone else. Our Web Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and WhenU will not knowingly collect personally-identifying information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please don't provide any information about yourself while visiting this Web Site. 

Back to top

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

Personally-Identifiable Information. The only personally-identifiable information we collect is information that our visitors voluntarily provide to us when using our Web Site. For example, if you are an advertiser and use our Web Site to request a contact from our sales department, we will ask for your name, email address and other contact information so that a WhenU sales representative or, in some cases, a WhenU reseller, can respond to your inquiry. Consumers and partners can use our Web Site to request technical support or other information from WhenU or to comment about any aspect of our operations. We use the contact information they provide to respond to their inquiries. We will not sell or rent to third parties information you may choose to provide through our online information request forms or use such information for purposes unrelated to your request for information or comments. We will not combine personally-identifiable information that you may choose to disclose through this Web Site with information about you that is available from any other source. If you want to contact WhenU but do not wish to reveal information about yourself online, you can reach a WhenU representative by telephone at 212-239-0000, or write to us at:

**WhenU.com, Inc.  
1 Penn Plaza, Suite 4532  
New York, NY 10119  
U.S.A.** **Transactional Information**

If you visit our Web Site and purchase one of the WhenU products, we will collect the information from you necessary to complete your transaction, including your name and credit card number, credit card expiration date and billing address. You will receive an order confirmation, subscription renewal notices, and promotional mailings about other WhenU products. If you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional mailings about WhenU products, follow the unsubscribe instructions provided within the email. We do retain your credit card information for the purpose of renewing your subscription. 

**Browser Level Information and IP Addresses**   
Our Web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our Web Site, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running and your IP address. Your IP address is a numerical address that is used by all computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. We use your IP address to deliver our Web pages to you on request. On occasion, we may also use your IP address for troubleshooting purposes to help diagnose problems with our server. The browser-level information we collect is stored in an anonymous form and is not linked to your personally-identifiable information. We use the browser level information we collect to make our Web Site as useful as we can for as many users as possible. 

**Cookies**   
A standard feature of browser software enables Web site publishers to place a small text file called a "cookie" on a visitor's hard drive. Our cookies don't reveal personal information; the only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you voluntarily supply. We use a cookie to remember the user name and login ID entered by advertisers and partners to access the external reporting system operated on a secure area of our Web Site. A cookie is inserted for this purpose only if the advertiser or partner has selected the "remember me" feature when he or she entered a password and login ID. We also use a cookie to authenticate users' login information as they navigate the reporting system pages of our Web Site. We do not use cookies to collect any personally-identifiable information and we do not track any of your activity on the Internet outside of our Web Site. For example, we do not use cookies to track which Web sites our visitors come from when they enter our site or which sites they go to when they leave our site. We use the services of a third-party software vendor to improve the performance of our Web site. This vendor assigns cookies to users' machines that help us manage traffic on our Web site. These cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.   
We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. 

Back to top

**DISCLOSURES OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**

WhenU is the sole owner of the information gathered through this Web Site. We will not sell or rent your personally-identifiable information to third parties and we will share your information with others only under the circumstances described below: 

**Credit Card Payments**   
WhenU uses a third-party credit card processing company to process payments for products purchased on our Web Site. If you order a product on our Web Site, we will share your credit card and billing information with this processing company to complete your transaction. The credit card processor that we use is not authorized to retain, share, store or use your credit card or billing information for purposes unrelated to processing payment for the transactions that you initiated. 

**Sales Inquiries**

If you use our Web Site to request information about purchasing advertising services from WhenU, we may forward your inquiry and contact information to one of our third-party resellers if we believe that the reseller would be in the best position to assist you. Our resellers are not authorized to use your contact information for any reason other than to respond to your request for information about WhenU's services. 

**Service Providers**   
From time to time, WhenU may contract with third-party service providers to help us operate our site, conduct other aspects of our business, or improve the services that we provide to you. Some of these service providers may be given access to personally-identifiable information collected through this Web Site, but only if we deem such access to be necessary to perform the services that we request. In these circumstances, we will require our service providers to commit that they will not use the personally identifiable information they receive from WhenU for any purposes other than those dictated by us. 

**Other Disclosures**   
We reserve the right to release any information about our visitors when we form a good faith belief that such a release is necessary to comply with the law, subpoenas or other valid legal process, to cooperate with law enforcement agencies, to report or collect debts owed, or to protect the rights, property or safety of WhenU, our Web Site visitors, or others. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event that WhenU or substantially all of our assets are acquired by another company, the information that we collect from our Web Site visitors may be included among the transferred assets. 

Back to top

**SECURITY OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of any personally identifiable information collected through this Web Site. Information gathered by WhenU through our Web Site is stored within WhenU-controlled databases on servers maintained in protected environments. However, no physical or electronic security system is perfect and we therefore cannot guarantee the security of our servers or databases or guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

Back to top

**REVIEWING, UPDATING AND DELETING YOUR INFORMATION**

If you provide any personally identifiable information to us through this Web Site, you will have the opportunity to review, update, or delete your information at any time (except, of course, with respect to information that we do not store). To exercise these choices, please email your request or instructions to [privacy@whenumail.com](mailto:privacy@whenumail.com), or call us at 212-239-0000. 

Back to top

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

The Web is an evolving medium and WhenU reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If WhenU chooses to make material changes in the future, we will post a notice of these changes on our Web Site before they go into effect. If the changes include the addition of rights to use or disclose previously-collected personally-identifiable information in a manner that was not described in this privacy policy at the time of collection through this Web Site, we will notify you using the email address or other contact information you have provided. In these circumstances, you will have an opportunity to delete your information or otherwise exercise a choice as to whether we use or disclose your information in this different manner. By using our Web Site, you agree that your visit and any dispute over privacy is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Visitor Agreement. 

Back to top

**LINKS**

Our Web Site may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content of those sites or for the privacy practices of their operators. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by WhenU on our Web Site, [http://www.whenu.com](http://www.whenu.com/). 

Back to top
